Guide to the Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society Papers 1835-1980 (Bulk 1840-1970) MS 74
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Journals, Annual Reports, and Printed Materials
  - Subseries 3: Printed Materials
    - "The Basis of Union of the Congregational Christian Churches and the Evangelical and Reformed Church with Interpretations", 1949 (Box 31)
    - "An Adventure in Liberty: A Short History of the Congregational Christian Churches", 1950 (Box 31)
    - "Between Hell's Kitchen and San Juan Hill: A Survey", 1952 (Box 31)
    - "Historical Sketches of the Congregational Christian Churches and the Evangelical and Reformed Church", 1955 (Box 31)
    - "'United in Christ': The Union of the Congregational Christian Churches and the Evangelical and Reformed Church", 1955 (Box 31)
    - "Step by Step with Our Congregational Christian Churches, Associations and Conferences Toward the Achievement of the Proposed United Church of Christ", 1955 (Box 31)
    - "United Church of Christ: History and Program", undated (Box 31)
    - L. Wendell Fifield, "What it Means to be a Member of the Congregational Church, Commission on Evangelism and Devotional Life", undated (Box 31)
    - "It Began with the Mayflower. Some Notes on Congregational Christian Organization", undated (Box 31)
    - "Good Fellowship Songs", undated (Box 31)
    - The Church Woman, 1977 (Box 31)
    - "Contrary Winds and Other Sermons", 1883 (Box 32)
    - The Limitations of Life and Other Sermons, 1880 (Box 31)
    - Susan Hayes Ward, The History of the Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1901 (Box 33)
    - Lewis S. Judd, The Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1901-1915, 1917 (Box 33)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, History of the Broadway Tabernacle Church of New York City, 1940 (Box 33)
    - Wade Arnold, A Brief Narrative History of the Broadway United Church of Christ, undated (Box 33)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of Preface for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 1 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 2 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 3 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 4 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 5 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 6 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 7 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 9 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 10 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Draft of chapter 11 for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, [1939-1940] (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, Notes for History of Broadway Tabernacle Church, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - L. Nelson Nichols, personal letter, 1912 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Centenary Dates, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Chronology after 1900, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1897, 1939, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Draft Sheets, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Directory, 1903 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1904 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1920 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1924 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1927 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1936 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1938 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1940 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1942 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1943 (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Directory, [1978] (Box 35)
    - Directory, 1980 (Box 35)
    - Guest Book, part 1, 4 January 1959-3 November 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Guest Book, part 2, 4 January 1959-3 November 1963 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Guest Book, part 1, 10 November 1963-12 July 1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Guest Book, part 2, 10 November 1963-12 July 1967 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1898-October 1917 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, November 1937-Fall 1940 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, January 1941-Spring 1943 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, Fall 1944-Spring 1947 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, 22 September 1950-17 December 1952 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, 14 January 1953-29 December 1954 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Tidings, 12 January 1955-11 December 1957 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Tidings, 8 January 1958-September 1962 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Tidings, January 1963-December 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Tidings, January 1967-December 1968 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Tidings, January 1969-October 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Tidings News and Notes, January 1972-May 1974 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1898-June 1916 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1898-June 1901 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1901-June 1904 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1904-June 1907 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1907-June 1910 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1910-June 1913 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1913-June 1916 (Box 39)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1916-June 1928 (Box 40)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1916-June 1919 (Box 40)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1919-June 1922 (Box 40)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1922-June 1925 (Box 40)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1925-June 1928 (Box 40)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1928-March 1948 (Box 41)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1928-June 1930 (Box 41)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, October 1930-March 1934 (Box 41)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, Fall 1934-Spring 1940 (Box 41)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, Fall 1941-January 1948 (Box 41)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Tidings, January 1948-March 1948 (Box 41)
    - Worship Materials, Broadway Congregational Church, "Selections for Worship," for use by women's fellowship groups, undated (Box 42)
    - Worship Materials, Broadway Congregational Church, "The Broadway Congregational Church, United Church of Christ," a collection of services, 1958-1959 (Box 42)
    - Arnold Wade, "An Interpretation of the Order of Worship at Broadway United Church of Christ", undated (Box 42)
    - Christmas Anniversary Sunday School Program, Sunday School number 2, 1840 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Program sponsored by BroTab, 1843 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Program sponsored by BroTab, [1846-1849] (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Program sponsored by BroTab, 1848 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Programs sponsored by BroTab, 1915-1929 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Programs, Announcements, Invitations, 1899-1940 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Programs sponsored by Broadway United Church of Christ, [1960-1979] (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Order of Service, 1859 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Programs of Services, 1902-1917 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Programs of Services, 1930-1940 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Programs of Services and Announcements, 1957-1973 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Installation Service: Reverend Bonnie Rosborough, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Sixtieth Anniversary Celebration of BroTab, 1840-1900, 1901 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Services in Dedication of the BroTab Cornerstone, 1903, 1905 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary, BroTab, 1840-1915 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - One Hundredth Anniversary, BroTab, 1840-1940 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - One Hundredth Anniversary, BroTab, 1938-1940 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Nichols's History, One Hundredth Anniversary, BroTab, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - One Hundredth Anniversary: Nichols's History, Publication Issues, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Anna Louise White, "A Metropolis in the Making, NYC, 1840", 1938-1940 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - "Fifty Years at Broadway and 56th Street", 1955 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Services: Celebration of Change, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - One Hundred Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, Broadway Universal Christian Church, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Ordinations, 1906-1971 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Series II: Papers
  This series contains thirty-four boxes.
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Proceedings against Lewis Tappan, 1839 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Letters prior to Church organization to David Hale, 1840 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, D. Hale Letter (copy), 1840 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - On the Installation of Reverend E. W. Andrews, 1841 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - List of Deeds, [1836-1846] (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Early real estate documents from David Hale, 1836-1846 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Account of David Hale with BroTab, 1841-1849 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Documents of David Hale versus John C. Cass, 1846-1848 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Letters from Reverend J.P. Thompson, 1844-1845 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Letter signed by Reverend J.P. Thompson, G.B. Cheer, and Henry Ward Beecher, 1851 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Deeds from sale of pews, [1845] (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Early documents and deeds, [1835-1851] (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Election of original trustees, 1840 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Election of trustees, 1841-1851 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, Minutes, Annual Reports, Letters, 1841-1850 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, Correspondence and Notices, 1846-1849 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Receipts after sale of church, 1850 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - List of items deposited in cornerstone, cornerstone metal plate (later removed), 1857 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Letter regarding Christe Street Church from David Hale, 1848 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Building specifications: First Free Congregational Church, Christe Street near Delancey, 1844 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Building specifications: First Free Congregational Church of New York, [1844-1849] (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Sundry Reports, 1854-1865 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Committees of the Church, 1852-1859 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Report of Committee upon the alteration of the standing rules, February 28, 1860 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Report of Pastor and Delegates regarding Church of the Puritans, 1861 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Report of Committee on the Centre Street Mission, 1863 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Regarding Congregational Church at Harlem, 1863 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Pews and Deeds, 1839-1858 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Receipts of Payment, 1847-1849 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Deacons' Fund and Reports, 1843-1878 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Invitations and Requests from other churches, 1844-1860 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Mortgages held, [1855-1863] (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Collateral Bond, 1859 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Mortgages, 1863 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Mortgages and Bonds, 1874-1876 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Treasurer's Correspondence and Report: Building Fund, 1857 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Special Meetings: Ratification of Sale of Property, 23 February 1857 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Contracts and Agreements (building), 1857-1858 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Estimates (building), 1857-1858 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, newspaper clipping: dedication of new church, [1859] (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, unsuccessful estimates, 1858 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, survey of grounds, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Notice of Annual Meetings, 1846-1923 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Election of Trustees, 1863-1888 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Registry of Marriages, 1867-1869 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Papers: Excommunication of T.E. Smith, 1862-1863 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Assorted Letters and Documents, 1855-1869 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Assorted Letters and Documents, 1870-1876 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Assorted Letters and Documents, 1877-1886 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Church Departments: Education, 1873-1879 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Department of Poor and Sick: Charities and Visitations, 1870-1879 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Department of Strangers, 1872-1878 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Department of Charitable Collections, 1871-1879 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Ecclesiastical Council, 1852, 1874, 1883 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, [Littlejohn history], [1862] (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, Mortgage, 1876 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers: Building Agreements, 1855-1858 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Bills and Receipts, 1858-1859 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Bills and Receipts, 1859 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Bills and Receipts, 1859-1860 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Cancelled Notes, 1861-1867 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Bills and Receipts, 1868 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Bills and Receipts, 1872-1873 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Building Fund, 1872 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Notebooks: Building Fund, Subscription Fund, 1872-1878 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Church of the Pilgrim, 48th Street: Papers, 1852-1867 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Church of the Pilgrim, 48th Street: Insurance Policies, 1859-1865 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Church of the Pilgrim, 48th Street: Articles of Agreement, 1859-1867 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Resolutions and Opinions on Voter Policies, 1854-1860 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers, 1855-1856 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers: Annual Report, 1858 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers: Annual Report, 1859 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers: Annual Report, 1859-1860 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers: Annual Report, 1860-1861 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Papers: Annual Report, 1861-1862 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Committee Report on Mission Church in Upper New York City, 1865 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Letters from Reverend Thompson, 1866 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, John Gray: Church Business, 1855-1867 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, John Gray: Correspondence, 1870-1872 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, John Gray: Letters from L.C. Moore, 1870-1872 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, John Gray: "My Dear Father", 1872 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, John Gray: "My Dear Husband", 1872 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, John Gray: Church Business, 1872-1876 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Letter: Reverend William Taylor, 1871 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, "Supplies" for Reverend William Taylor, 1872 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1842-1857 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1859-1878 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1863-1877 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1879-1888 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1899-1904 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1905-1912 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1913-1916 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1917-1920 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1921-1924 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasurer's Reports, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Receipts for Contributions, 1846-1859 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1840-1846 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1845-1847 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1849-1850 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1850-1852 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1850-1852 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1856-1858 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1867, 1869 November (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Receipt Book, 1868-1872 (Box 51)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1869-1870 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1871 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1871 November 1-1872 November 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1872 November 1-1873 November 1 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1873 November 1-1874 November 1 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1874 November-1875 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1875 November 1-1876 November 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1876 November 1-1877 November 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1877 November 1-1878 November 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1878 November 1-1879 November 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Treasury Vouchers, 1880-1884 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Absentee Roll Book, 1848-1927 (Box 53)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Original Certificate: David Hale and 50 Members: #1-#51, 1840 August 15 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #52-#101, 1840 August-1841 January (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #102-#152, 1841 January-1841 July (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #153-#200, 1841 July-1841 December (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #201-#289, 1841 October-1842 April (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #290-#311, 1842 April-1842 September (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #312, 1838 May (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #313-#386, 1842 October-1842 November (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #387-#445, 1842 July-1844 May (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #446-#501, 1843 May-1845 June (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #502-#619, 1845 October-1847 August (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: [#620]-#711, 1847 August-1849 December (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #716-#760, 1850 February-1851 May (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #761-#842, 1851 August-1853 February (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #843-#911, 1853 March-1855 September (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #912-#1030, 1855 September-1858 May (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #1031-#1133, 1858 May-1859 November (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #1134-#1216, 1859 November-1861 May (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #1217-#1320, 1861 June-1862 May (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Certificates: #1321-#1455, 1862 July-1864 December (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Correspondence: Requests for Dismissals, 1840-1848 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Correspondence: Requests for Dismissals, 1846-1851 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Correspondence: Requests for Dismissals, 1850-1852 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Correspondence: Requests for Dismissals, 1852-1853 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Correspondence: Requests for Dismissals, 1853-1855 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Membership Correspondence: Requests for Dismissals, 1856-1861 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1853-1861 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1865 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1866-1868 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1871-1874 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1869-1878 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1878 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1876-1878 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Letters of Dismission, 1877-1879 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members unknown, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4202-#4296, 1906-1912 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4297-#4410, 1906-1912 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4411-#4556, 1906-1912 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4555-#4699, 1906-1912 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4204-#4838, 1906-1912 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1905-1906 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1907-1908 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1909-1910 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1911-1913 (Box 56, Folder 9)